{
    "subject": "resource/Carl_Braden",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathPlace",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Carl Braden died in the United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8329174518585205,
            "question": "Where did Carl Braden die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.820685625076294,
            "question": "When did Carl Braden die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7621160745620728,
            "question": "Was Carl Braden a citizen of the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4781316816806793,
            "question": "How did Carl Braden's death impact others?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3313043415546417,
            "question": "What is known about Carl Braden's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32737472653388977,
            "question": "Were there any significant events in Carl Braden's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27821487188339233,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Carl Braden?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.270597904920578,
            "question": "Was Carl Braden involved in any notable causes or organizations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2670365273952484,
            "question": "What was Carl Braden's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22581727802753448,
            "question": "Does anything else about Carl Braden's life stand out?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Carl Braden died in the United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6879_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Carl Braden's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6879_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Carl Braden involved in any notable causes or organizations?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6879_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Carl Braden?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6879_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6879_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6879_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6879_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6879_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6879_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6879_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6879_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6879_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6879_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6879_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n- The documents mention multiple individuals named Carl Braden, but all indicate that these individuals died in Tennessee or in hospitals in the United States (Chattanooga). Therefore, it can be reasonably inferred that Carl Braden died in the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The information given does not provide a clear indication of Carl Braden's death location outside the United States, nor does it contradict his death being within the country.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}